Guide to the Tony Judt Papers MC 233
New York University Archives
- Series IX: Multimedia (INTERNAL ONLY)
  - CO/FE/PO Colección de Trenes Fernández Pacheco Outeiriño, undated (Box 28)
    Corespondence - Chron. and Misc. - Declined Invitations, 2008
  - Zip Install Windows/DOS, 1995 (Box 28)
  - Zip Tools - Tools Disk Do Not Back-Up, undated (Box 28)
  - iomegaware, 2000 (Box 28)
  - iomegaware (2), 2000 (Box 28)
  - iomega Quick Floppy Copy, 2001 (Box 28)
  - iomega Application CD & User's Manual, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Sony Driver Recovery CD, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Sony System Recovery CD #1, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Sony System Recovery CD #2, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Sony Application Recovery CD, undated (Box 28)
  - iomega Tools Version GM5600, 1998 (Box 28)
  - The Book, 2003 May 29 (Box 28)
  - Judt - New Book, undated (Box 28)
  - Ma vision de l'Union européenne et de son avenir, 2005 (Box 28)
  - Prix Latsis Universitaires 2008 conference - DVD #1 (Box 28)
  - Prix Latsis Universitaires 2008 conference - "The Global Economic Outlook for Europe and the U.S." - DVD #1 (Box 28)
  - "De 6 à 27: qu'elle Europe?" confernece - DVD #1, 2007 (Box 28)
  - "De 6 à 27: qu'elle Europe?" conference - DVD #1, 2007 (Box 28)
  - José Manuel Barroso, "L'Avenir de l'Europe: entre rêve et réalité" - DVD #1, 2006 (Box 28)
    Journée Denis de Rougemont - Conférence organisée par le Centre européen de la culture sous le haut patronage du Recteur de l'Universite de Genève
  - Table ronde, "L'Avenir de l'Europe: entre rêve et réalité" - DVD #2, 2006 (Box 28)
  - Conférence du Professeur Dusan Sidjanski, "L'Union européenne face à la crise mondiale", 2009 (Box 28)
- Series IX: Multimedia
  The University Archives cannot currently provide access to the material in this series. Please contact the Archives for further information.
- Series X: Bibliography File, undated
  This series contains two boxes of 3x5 index cards with bibliographic information on primary and secondary source material filed topically. It is unclear whether the cards are tied to any specific work of Judt's or whether they comprise more of a general file he kept. Each entry in this series denotes titles on dividers within the index card boxes.
  - France: Trials + Related, undated (Box 29)
  - 19th c. material, undated (Box 29)
  - General 20th c. intells, undated (Box 29)
  - Fr. philosophy, undated (Box 29)
  - Memoirs, undated (Box 29)
  - Intells + Communism, undated (Box 29)
  - Fascism, undated (Box 29)
  - 40-44 collaboration, undated (Box 29)
  - Resistance + [illegible], undated (Box 29)
  - Nationalism regions + [illegible], undated (Box 29)
  - Anti-Am (Fr.), undated (Box 29)
  - Catholics, undated (Box 29)
  - Colonialism + Tiers Monde, undated (Box 29)
  - Jews, undated (Box 29)
  - Political [illegible] Thought, undated (Box 29)
  - Essays, undated (Box 29)
  - Feminism, undated (Box 29)
  - Cinema, undated (Box 29)
  - The Press, undated (Box 29)
  - Education, undated (Box 29)
  - Sociology + Anthrop., undated (Box 29)
  - Psychology + Language, undated (Box 29)
  - History, undated (Box 29)
  - Literature + Theatre, undated (Box 29)
  - European intells. + ideas 20th c., undated (Box 29)
  - E-W Intell. Division, undated (Box 29)
  - Ital. politics post-'43, undated (Box 29)
  - Italy: Intells + Comms, undated (Box 29)
  - Italy: Intells. 1943-1956, undated (Box 29)
  - Italy: Philosophy, undated (Box 29)
  - Italy: Anti-fascism, undated (Box 29)
  - Italy: Anti-Am, undated (Box 29)
  - Post-'56 in Italy, undated (Box 29)
  - France 20, undated (Box 29)
  - Cz. trials, undated (Box 30)
  - Czech History, undated (Box 30)
  - Cz. Intells, undated (Box 30)
  - Sudeten Issue, undated (Box 30)
  - Poland: History, undated (Box 30)
  - Poland: Trials, undated (Box 30)
  - E. Eur Intells [Exc. Cz], undated (Box 30)
  - Hung. Intells, undated (Box 30)
  - Hung. Trials, undated (Box 30)
  - Hung. History, undated (Box 30)
  - E. Germany History, undated (Box 30)
  - Rom + Bulg + Yug Trials, undated (Box 30)
  - Rom + Bulg History, undated (Box 30)
  - E. German Trials, undated (Box 30)
  - Moscow Trials, undated (Box 30)
  - 'General' Trials, undated (Box 30)
  - USSR + Cold War, undated (Box 30)
  - Yugoslavia History, undated (Box 30)
  - Cominform + C. Eur. 1940-56, undated (Box 30)
  - Archives, undated (Box 30)
  - France 18-19 c., undated (Box 30)